{
  "id": "005-questions",
  "title": "Questions & Answers",
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "kas",
      "choices": [
        "who",
        "what",
        "where",
        "when"
      ],
      "answer": "who",
      "tts": "kas"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "ką",
      "choices": [
        "what",
        "who",
        "where",
        "why"
      ],
      "answer": "what",
      "tts": "ką"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "kur",
      "choices": [
        "where",
        "when",
        "how",
        "who"
      ],
      "answer": "where",
      "tts": "kur"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "kada",
      "choices": [
        "when",
        "where",
        "why",
        "how"
      ],
      "answer": "when",
      "tts": "kada"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "kodėl",
      "choices": [
        "why",
        "when",
        "where",
        "who"
      ],
      "answer": "why",
      "tts": "kodėl"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "kas"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "ką"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "kur"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "kada"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "kodėl"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "taip",
      "choices": [
        "yes",
        "no",
        "maybe",
        "later"
      ],
      "answer": "yes",
      "tts": "taip"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "ne",
      "choices": [
        "no",
        "yes",
        "later",
        "always"
      ],
      "answer": "no",
      "tts": "ne"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "taip"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "ne"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "gerai",
      "choices": [
        "okay",
        "bad",
        "no",
        "later"
      ],
      "answer": "okay",
      "tts": "gerai"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "gerai"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "blogai",
      "choices": [
        "badly",
        "well",
        "good",
        "okay"
      ],
      "answer": "badly",
      "tts": "blogai"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "blogai"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "kaip",
      "choices": [
        "how",
        "why",
        "when",
        "where"
      ],
      "answer": "how",
      "tts": "kaip"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "kaip"
    }
  ]
}